musculardevelopment.com 2006-05-14

# Muscular Development Magazine

**MuscularDevelopment.com Privacy Policy:**  

Muscular Development (MuscularDevelopment.com), a division of Advanced Research Press, Inc., knows that you care about how your Personal Information is collected, stored, shared, and used. We value your trust and will work hard to ensure that any Personal Information in our possession is handled carefully and professionally. By visiting MuscularDevelopment.com you are accepting the Privacy Policy described herein.  

MuscularDevelopment.com will not collect Personal Information like your name, email, mailing address and telephone number without your knowledge and permission; and we will take reasonable steps to protect the security of the Personal Information we do collect from you.  

**Information We Collect**  
MuscularDevelopment.com collects general, non-personally identifiable information each time a customer visits our web site. This information is used to allow us to understand how our site is used and helps us to continually improve the service we offer and make the features on our web site easier to use. We may share aggregate, non-personally identifiable information about our visitors with our vendors, partners and other third parties to this end.  

When you decide to place an order or conduct a transaction with MuscularDevelopment.com, we will collect Personal Information about you that you voluntarily share with us. We collect Personal Information that is necessary for us to provide you with the services and/or products offered on our site. This Personal Information may include your name, email and mailing address, telephone number and credit card information.   

**How We Use Cookies**  
A "cookie" is a small piece of information sent by a web server to store on a web browser so it can later be read back from that browser. This is useful for having the browser remember some specific information. MuscularDevelopment.com uses cookies to improve your shopping experience with us.   

**Use and Sharing of Information**  
MuscularDevelopment.com considers the Personal Information it retains important to you and our business and treat it accordingly. We share your email address, mailing address, phone number, or credit card information only as it is necessary to provide to other companies that perform various functions necessary to operate our business - for example, to process credit cards. We will share with these other companies only that Personal Information they require to fulfill their contractual obligations to us. These companies agree that they will not use or disclose that Personal Information for any other purpose.  

We may have third party advertisers on our site. These advertisers may use cookies to track general, non-personally identifiable information about the ads you have seen and types of things that you appear interested in. We do not share any Personal Information about you with these advertisers unless you give us permission to do so separate from any permission you provide during the registration process. However, these advertisers may have other sources of information and their own privacy practices. These advertisers may also use combined information about your visits to our site and other sites in order to provide advertisements about related goods and services that you may be interested in. When you visit a site that we advertise on, we may place a cookie on your computer.  

From time to time, MuscularDevelopment.com may contact you by mail or email to make you aware of special offers, new services and other information we believe to be of interest. We also may send you an email confirmation/receipt when you conduct a transaction on our web site, and additional email or mail notification if necessary to provide subsequent information on status of a transaction on our web site, and occasional customer surveys to evaluate our performance with you.  

Occasionally, we send emails to select customers on behalf of carefully selected businesses. We do not provide these businesses with any Personal Information such as your name and address. If you do not wish to receive such offers, please notify us with the customer service link below.  

We always give you the choice to opt-out from receiving non-transaction based email such as advertisements, updates and promotions. If you do not opt-out from receiving these communications about our site, we will send them to you. If you prefer not to receive non-transaction based email from us, please contact us and we will remove you from our email list. Please note that these requests may take 5-10 days to process.  

**How We Store Your Information**  
MuscularDevelopment.com makes every reasonable effort to keep your Personal Information safe and secure. We also protect the connection between your computer and our server through industry-standard encryption technology known as Secure Socket Layer (SSL) when you place an order with us.   

**Links to Other Web Sites**  
MuscularDevelopment.com may contain links to external web sites that have privacy policies different from ours. We have no control or responsibility for other web sites and recommend that you read each privacy policy prior to taking advantage of any offers.   

**Merger, Sale or Transfer Of Ownership**  
In the event that MuscularDevelopment.com is merged, disposed of, or sold in part or in full, customer Personal Information could be one of the assets that are transferred and your Personal Information may be accessed by a successor or purchaser. In such event, your Personal Information will remain subject to the Muscular Development Privacy Policy in effect at such time.  

**Compliance with Law and Protection of Others**  
MuscularDevelopment.com may release account and other personal information when we believe it is appropriate or required to comply with the law or protect the rights, property, or safety of MuscularDevelopment.com, our users, or others. This may include exchanging information with other entities for fraud protection and to reduce credit risk.   

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**  
Our privacy policy may be revised at any time. To stay informed about changes to our privacy policy, please check this page.  

**Contact Information**  
MuscularDevelopment.com is operated by Advanced Research Press, Inc.  

Our mailing address is:  
Advanced Research Press  
690 Route 25A  
Setauket, NY 11733  

Our telephone number is 631-751-9696.  

If you have any questions or comments regarding our Privacy Policy, please [contact us via email.](mailto:customerservice@musculardevelopment.com)
